pdf.live 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy - PDF.live

PDF.live ("Website") is a website owned and operated by Tightrope Interactive, Inc. ("Company"). 

The Company takes privacy matters very seriously. This document explains what type of data we are collecting and how we are using this data. This document pertains to the usage of our website. 

### What personal identifiable information does the Company store?

Personally Identifiable Information is data that identifies you personally; such as your address, name, email address, telephone number, or birth date. The Company does not collect or store any Personally Identifiable Information from this website.

### What non-personally identifiable information does the Company store?

Non Personally Identifiable Information is data that cannot be used to identify a specific person. Examples of NPII can include items such as IP Address, the type of Web Browser you are using, the version of the web browser, the Operating System you are using and other websites you may have visited.

The Company retains some non-personally identifiable information to improve our website and for statistical purposes. 

### Do you use cookies?

A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer’s hard drive for record keeping purposes.

When you visit our website, the Company may store a cookie on your computer to identify you; such cookie identifies that you previously visited this website, and allows us to analyze our web traffic to improve our services and better serve our visitors.

### Web beacons or Pixels

Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. We embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

We may use web beacons on our site to help track consumers that have visited our website in order to help improve our site.

### How is the information processed?

The Company collects and processes non-personal information in order to allow better service and monitor use of our site. This information is collected by our web server logs and web beacons.

### How We Use Your Information

We use NPII to help us understand who is visiting our website and what they do on our website. This data is then used to help us improve our site, it's content and performance.

### How We Share Your Information

We may share NPII data with third parties for the purpose of analyzing the data and help[ing us improve our website. An example of this is our usage of Google Analytics to aggregate NPII data and proivide insights on what consumers are doing on our web site.

### Children's Online Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit the Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act"). For more information about the Act and children’s on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC’s web site at www.ftc.gov/privacy. For safety tips on privacy visit www.OnGuardOnline.gov.

### Policy Updates

We may change this privacy policy. If we change this policy we will post the changes to this privacy statement, our websites’ homepages, and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

 **Enforcement / Redress**

If you feel that we have not followed our Privacy Policy, please let us know. Also, if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, its implementation, or would like a written copy, please feel free to contact us at:

Tightrope Interactive, Inc. 588 Sutter St #551, San Francisco, CA 94102 

Alternatively, if you would like, contact us via e-mail at webmaster@PDF.live
